今天都挺太平?
All quiet today?
不会出什么篓子 头儿
Keeping it like that, boss.
有我们在就没问题
We rule where we stand.
这些地方的各个角落都有警察
Police sitting on all corners over these parts.
很可能是因为我们抛尸来着
Likely because we been dropping bodies.
是啊 他们就是这样
Yeah, they do like that.
但是 你知道  明天就会有个黑人在别的什么地方中枪...
But, you know, tomorrow some other nigga'll stop a bullet somewhere else...
那时他们就换地方蹲点儿了
and then they'll go stand on a new spot.
Boy Marlo把商店关了
Boy Marlo closed up shop.
道上说 他现在搞批发了
Word is, he wholesaling his packages for now.
他现在外面都没马仔了?
He don't have no crews out here at all?
他街角的生意怎么办?
How about his avenue corners?
那黑鬼闪得够快的 是吧?
Nigga give up quick, didn't he?
妈的 我刚开始有点尊敬这小王八蛋的忠心
Damn, I was just beginning to respect the little motherfucker for showing heart.
好了 听着
All right, listen.
他们警察一滚 你们就都过去夺回我的地盘
When them police roll out, y'all step in there and take my corners.
我办事你放心  B
I'm on it, B.
Bill's的乳酪牛排
Cheese steaks from Bill's.
不去 我周二刚吃过 兄弟
Nah, I did that Tuesday, man.
操 你选吧
Fuck it then, you pick.
不是吧 我他妈见鬼了
No, fuck me.
怎么了?
What?
开车闲逛的那个
Mope in the truck.
他怎么了?
What about him?
我好像抓过他
Think I locked him up.
- 是吗? - 是啊  叫Avon啥啥的?
- Yeah? - Yeah. Avon what's-his-face?
帮会里的大佬
Big player from the projects.
他是我几年前所在分队的主要目标
He was the target on that detail I worked a couple of years back,
我跟你说起过
the one I told you about.
混蛋已经出来了
Motherfucker's out already.
怎么 判了他几年?
Why, what'd he pull?
哦 6年还是8年 谁他妈还记得?
Oh, six, eight years. Who the fuck can remember?
他关了两年就出来了?
And he's out in two?
也许我记错刑期了
Maybe I got the years wrong.
我要说的是 那家伙是个混蛋 把他关起来 就这样
My point is, guy's an asshole. Locked him up, is all.
市场的二号人物?
Pit B from the market.
看吧 现在你像个警察一样思考了
See, now you're thinking like police.
火线重案组 第三季 第7集
the.wire.s03e07
* When you walk through the garden *
* you gotta watch your back *
* well I beg your pardon *
* walk the straight and narrow track *
* if you walk with Jesus *
* he's gonna save your soul *
* you gotta keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
* he's got the fire and the fury *
* at his command *
* well you don't have to worry *
* if you hold on to Jesus hand *
* we'll all be safe from Satan *
* when the thunder rolls *
* just gotta help me keep the devil *
* way down in the hole *
* you gotta help me keep the devil *
良心是有代价的     ——Butchie
计划有变
Change in plan.
Bell 你认识
Bell, you recognize.
第二个目标是Marlo Stanfield...
Second target is a Marlo Stanfield...
很显然  他在和Bell争夺西边的地盘
who's apparently warring with Bell for the West Side corners.
那Kintel Williamson呢?
What about Kintel Williamson?
那个案子现在暂停调查
That case is on hold for now.
暂停调查?
On hold?
我们刚查出他两个手下的电话
We just managed to ID the cell phones on two of his people.
- 尽管如此... - 我是说 为什么不再给几个星期...
- Be that as it may... - I mean, why not take a few more weeks...
我们就能搞定从Kintel那里 得到的线索 你知道吗?
so we can put together that we got on Kintel, you know?
我们把这案子送交大陪审团 然后再着手办西区这个案子
We send the case to grand jury and then we start up this West Side case.
不然 我们就浪费了两个多星期...
Otherwise, we wasted more than two months...
让我们改变调查目标 是局长和副局长的意思
Change of target comes to us from the Commissioner and the Deputy Ops.
警局现在要先发制人
The Department is in a reactive mode
采取一切必要手段来 降低谋杀发生率
trying to get the murder rate down by any means necessary.
Kintel两个月前抛尸
Kintel was dropping bodies two months ago.
现在是西区让头儿们焦头烂额
Today, it's the West Side that's got the bosses spinning.
听着 我知道 你们都觉得我整天地蹲在屋顶上...
Look, I know y'all thought it was nothing for me to sit on that roof...
顶着烈日躲着成群的虫子之类的...
day after 90-degree day...
没什么了不起  但是 该死的 这是功亏一篑
dodging swarms of cicadas and shit, but, damn, this is fucked up!
所有我对Kintel有价值的调查
And all the assets work I did on Kintel,
他的车 他的资金流动...
his cars, his cash flow...
都直接扔进抽屉了?
just put that in a drawer?
总有一天  我要为真正的警察局工作
Someday, I wanna work for a real police department.
就看他们办的事有多操蛋  你知道吗?
Just to see how the fuck they do it, you know?
McNulty
McNulty.
到我办公室来
In my office.
嘿 Prez 能帮我查点东西吗?
Hey, Prez, can you run something out for me?
什么?
What?
我要知道谁订了这个房间
I need to know who rented this room
在市中心的Hilton 上上周四
in the downtown Hilton, Thursday before last.
-谁订了这个房间?  -嗯哼
- Who rented the room? - hmm.
地址 信用卡记录 所有你能查到的
Address, credit card details, whatever you can pull.
这和案子有什么关系?
How's it fit with the case?
现在还不好说
It's hard to say just yet.
嘿 伙计 我修剪完了
Hey, my man. I'm done mowing.
所以呢?
So?
我想我应该用这个
I figured I'd use this
沿着栅栏把草坪边缘修剪一下
to edge the weeds around the fence.
这要用汽油
It's gas-powered.
那我用着没问题
Means I gotta prime it.
你教我一遍就行了
You ain't gotta school me but once.
先喝点水再接着干吧
Get some water before you go back out there.
好吧
All right.
你干活很卖力
You been going hard at it.
你一直在合适的时候出现 我就会一直用你
You keep showing up at the spot, I'll keep putting you on.
好啊 反正我也一无所有
Good, 'cause I ain't got nothing else.
你是从老地方回来的 对吧?
You walked back through them old doors, didn't you?
是试过去那里
Tried to.
嗯 我还以为你不会回来了
Yeah. I had took you for gone.
老兄 那些保释官
Man, parole officers,
职业介绍所
employment agencies.
妈的 我觉得自己好像 打扰了他们午休似的
Shit, I just felt like I was an interruption to their lunch break.
没有家人吗?
No family?
除了我奶奶没别人了
None besides my grandmother.
她留我在地下室过夜
She put me up in her basement.
这要求对那老人来说也挺过分的了
That's plenty to ask of the old girl right there.
除了你奶奶  你还可以找别人谈谈
You could use somebody to talk to besides your grand-moms.
他们那些社工呢?
What about one of them social worker types?
我和一哥们儿来往过
I hooked up with one dude.
他人挺不错的
He was cool.
不过 我还没准备好
But, I wasn't ready.
现在你看起来准备好了
You look like you're ready now.
我是说 你要是能找个人聊聊 就不用跟我说了
I mean, you found an ear to bend, you wouldn't have to talk to me.
妈的 我知道你会看烦了我这丑货
Shit, I know you gonna get tired of looking at my ugly-ass grill.
喝这么快 你会抽筋的
Drink that too fast, you'll cramp up.
- 你问我? - 是的
- You're asking? - I am.
- 队长 我没有... - 我对改变调查目标没意见
- Lieutenant, I didn't... - Because I got no problem changing targets
如果是上头让我这么做
if that's what the bosses tell me to do.
除非这涉及到个人 像Kima中枪的时候...
Unless it's personal, like when Kima got shot...
那样的话 我会不惜一切代价
I don't care where we spend our time and money.
Bell也好 Williamson也好 无论是谁 对我来说都只是警务工作
Bell, Williamson, whoever. It's all just police work to me.
而且我明白 那些工资等级比我高的人...
And I understand that people above my pay grade...
有权做出他们的决定
have the right to make decisions  that are theirs to make.
- 如果他们错了呢? - 那他们就是错了
- And if they're wrong? - Then they're wrong.
时间会证明一切 不是吗?
And time will tell, won't it?
现在 我要你告诉我真相
Now, I'm asking you for the truth.
你背着我去找Colvin
You went to Colvin behind my back.
我得自己去虎穴啊
I'd have gone to the devil himself.
你做出什么选择 队长
Which way you were standing, Lieutenant,
跟我屁关系都没有
had not a fucking thing to do with it.
你这个混蛋
You piece of shit.
我必须这么做
I did it 'cause it had to be done.
就像两年前我们 第一次被分派的时候一样
Just like it had to be done two years ago when we were first detailed.
我们那时候要抓Stringer  现在也一样
Stringer was the target then, he's still the target now.
队长 你知道吗
Lieutenant, you know,
在上头看来 你出类拔萃...
as bosses go, you're better than most...
我也知道你特意把我从航务处调出来
and I know you went out of your way to get me off that boat.
我都知道  但现在我们一定要抓住这个人
I know that, but now we're back on the right man.
McNulty警探
Detective McNulty.
等一抓着Stringer
When the cuffs go on Stringer,
你就另谋高就吧
you need to find a new home.
你在这个小组没有未来了
You're done in this unit.
- 总数对吗? - 是 这一批货差点就去了Richmond了
- Your count right? - Yeah, went almost to Richmond for this here batch.
嗯 我听着呢
Yeah, I'm holding.
- 你是按我们说的做的 是吧? - 是
- You did like we say, right? - Yeah.
给他吧
Give him that.
过几天我们还要60个
We're gonna need another 60 more in a couple days.
- 还要60个? - 你知道我们怎么干
- 60 more? - You know how we do.
所以别大惊小怪的 Bernard
So, don't be crying, Bernard.
你肯定漏掉什么了
You must have left something out.
操 没有 我一个个地从每个地段每个岗位收集来数据
Fuck, no.I got the part ones from every sector, every post.
我们下降了大概2%
We're down about 2%.
不对 具体都哪里下降了?
No, where exactly are we down?
盗窃和入室盗窃的比率没什么变化
Larcenies and burglaries are steady.
但是枪击案和袭击总数都下降了
But shootings and agg assaults are both down.
因毒品被拘留的也少了  不过我猜情况没这么好
Drug arrests, too, but I guess that won't look so good.
我是说 在这片地区  地理上都哪些地方下降了?
I mean, where geographically are we down, in the district?
指定毒品区附近的地方上升了
Well, the posts near the designated drug zones are up,
几乎所有的都是
almost all of them.
虽然不是很好  不过其他地方都下降了
That ain't pretty, but everywhere else it's down.
有些地方下降了4%
In some places as much as 4%.
上头会爱死你的
Bosses gonna love you.
现在接受表扬为时过早
It's too soon to take any credit.
这个是 你称之为什么来着?
This might be, what you call that?
统计异常
A statistical aberration.
你打算让他们知道 你的小尝试可能奏效了不?
You ain't gonna let them know that your little experiment might be working?
还不到时候 不
Not yet, no.
但我要告诉他们 我们准备干什么
But I'll tell you what we are gonna do.
从下个星期开始
Starting next week,
你去从每个地段治安稳定的岗位...
I want you to pull one car out of service...
调一辆巡逻车  一天三班的都要调
in the quiet posts in every sector, all three shifts.
我要那9个人...
We'll take those nine guys...
让他们都去犯罪高发的岗位
then use them and double up on the high crime posts.
如果犯罪高危区变少了...
If we handle less of it...
那么管那些罪案就容易多了 对吧?
we ought to do better with the crime we got, right?
能给我两个一次性手机吗?
Can I get two Trac disposable phones?
现在特价
They're on special.
4个180
Four for $180.
就要两个
Just the two.
晚上的演出在Westview 8点45
The late show out at Westview is 8:45.
要是今天不用跑完全程 我们还能赶上演出
We could make that if we don't make the whole damn run today.
在我看来 一个电话就够用了
Seem to me one phone is as good as the next.
没生意的时候 只有傻瓜才会开车满世界转悠
Only a fool would drive all over the world when there ain't no need.
你要是还那么多废话 我就把你扔在巴尔的摩
Keep on with that shit and I'm gonna leave your ass in Baltimore.
我可不放心一男人自己上路 知道吗?
I don't trust no man on the road by hisself, okay?
我可不傻
I'm not stupid.
傻逼
Stupid-ass fucker.
局长!
Commissioner!
怎么样?
How goes it?
告诉你吧 在市长的内阁会议之前 事情进展很顺利
It went a lot better before the Mayor's cabinet meeting, I can tell you that.
他搞你了?
He rip you?
他说我们今年要控制在300以内
Says we need to finish under 300 for this year,
不管情况如何
regardless of how it happens.
- 现在 我试着告诉... - Erv 我问你
- Now, I tried to tell... - Erv, let me ask you.
你们的人对证人协助事务怎么看?
Where do you guys stand on this Witness Assistance thing?
什么?
What?
全面整改城市的证人协助计划?
Overhauling the city's Witness Assistance Program?
关于证人可能因此被杀的问题...
Nobody from the Mayor's office called you...
市长办公室没人给你打电话?
regarding this problem of witnesses getting killed?
打过 一星期前幕僚长给我打过电话
I got a call from Chief of Staff a week ago, yeah.
但是他都在说我应该努力防止 更多的证人被杀
But all he said was I should try not to have any more witnesses get killed.
但全面整改计划?
But overhauling the program?
除非有人愿意提供大笔资金...
Unless someone wants to spend a lot more money...
否则我可没那么多人去做这个
there's not a whole hell of a lot my people can do.
你还没和市长直接谈过这个问题?
And you haven't talked to the Mayor directly on this?
你不会是想在这事上整我吧?
You're not gonna fuck me on this?
现在 市长已经对我吹鼻子瞪眼睛了
As it is, I got the Mayor's teeth in my ass.
我不会提你的名字
Your name does not get mentioned.
市长没跟我透露半个字
Mayor didn't say a word to me.
谢了
Thanks.
这没什么
It's nothing.
这是特区第一 WPGC 95.5
This is DC 's number one, WPGC 95.5.
Burtonsville路 198 西Burtonsville
我们他妈现在在什么地方?
Where the fuck we at now?
就买四五个 Bernard
Just buy four or five, Bernard.
照我说的做 会快好多
Do it like that and it'll go twice as quick.
我要一个雪泥 Bernard  再来几个脆甜甜圈
I want a Shrek Slurpee, Bernard, and some Krispy Kreme.
这些都来自于同一个一次性手机 嗯?
All this from one disposable cell phone, huh?
现在已经坏了
And a dead one, too.
是Marlo的人在用 然后被Kima的线人捡走了
It was used by Marlo's people and picked up off the ground by Kima's CI.
可能是假消息 我们要核实
Problem is it's just raw data.We need to firm up...
从监视和线人获得的有关Marlo行动的消息
what we know about Marlo's operation with surveillance and CI info.
另一方面...
On the other hand...
如果我们有一个一次性手机 知道它是Stringer一个喽啰用过的...
if we had a burner that we knew was used by one of Stringer's players...
那么我们就可以利用 对那个组织所掌握的信息...
we could use what we know about that organization...
建立起各种联系
to make all kinds of connections.
只需一部好手机  我们就能恢复他们的联络网
Get us one good phone, we'll give you the network.
这是好消息
That's the good news.
那坏消息呢?
And what's the bad?
信息都是旧的
It's all historical.
我们能恢复联络网 这没问题...
We can give you the network, no problem...
但到那时网络就是一星期前的了 他们已经把手机扔了
but by then it's a week old and they've dumped their phones.
而且我们怎么连接起网络
And how we get a wire up on that,
我还没想出办法
I haven't figured out yet.
那就找出办法来 探员先生
Well, see that you do, Detective.
你要是一直干下去
Oh, yeah, you keep this job,
我就该长肉了
I'm gonna gain some serious weight.
- 就两个? - 就两个
- Just the two? - Just the two.
黑鬼 你从来都没听说过大量购买吧?
Nigga, you ain't never heard of buying in bulk?
你能给别人剩下很多钱
You could be saving them people all kind of money.
更好的是 都给我花
Better still, spending it on me.
- 你怎么有把枪 Bernard? - 哦 你没听说过?
- Why you got a gun, Bernard? - Oh, you ain't heard?
在Avon家 我们就装备上了
Avon's home, so we tooling up.
又不是就你一个人假释
You ain't the only one on parole.
你不要逼我发飙啊
You riding my last good nerve.
我还能逼你做别的哦
And that ain't the only thing I can ride.
我要早点回州际公路
Just get me back to the interstate.
白色大包 有白色大包的
Big white bag, got the big white bag.
哪个是他来着?
Which one is he again?
Broadus Bodie的外号
Broadus, street name of Bodie.
- 大白包 有大白包 - 他过去是个放贷的
- Big white, got the big white. - He used to be a low-rises.
后来进了高楼
Had a tower later on.
你觉得他还要用那个手机多久?
How many more minutes you think he's got on that phone?
不管了 咱们去酒吧
Fuck this, let's hit the bar.
Lester要手机 老兄
Lester needs a phone, man.
不 有更简单的办法
No, there's an easier way.
明天你就知道了
I'll show you tomorrow.
走吧
Come on.
我请客
I'm buying.
大白包 有大白包
Big white bag, got the big white bag.
她只是希望我高兴 你知道吗?
She just wants me to be happy, you know?
我是说 我也希望她是如此
And I mean, I do the same for her when I can.
就拿警察那事儿来说吧
Like this thing with the police detective.
Brianna想让我和她去市中心...
Brianna says she wants me to go downtown with her and...
我不知道  听那家伙说说D的事情
I don't know, hear the man out about D.
我知道那人肯定都是胡扯
And I know there ain't nothing to it,
但她很难过 你知道吗?
but she is all upset, you know?
我就试着告诉她你跟我说的
And I tried to tell her what you told me.
可是 她说她想去那里
But, she say she wanna go down there
亲自和他谈谈 我猜
and talk to him herself, I guess.
- 你跟她说了警察的事了? - 什么?
- You told her about the cop? - What?
那个警探
About the detective.
我跟你说的 你都告诉她了?
What you told me, you told her?
毕竟是她儿子 是吧?
It's her son, right?
我是说  她难道没有权利知道发生什么了吗?
I mean, ain't she got a right to know what's going on?
- 听着 我想... - 什么?
- Look, I just thought... - What?
你干嘛要让那些废话 让她难受?
Why the fuck you gonna get her all upset over some bullshit?
都他妈过去一年了  每个人都忘了那堆狗屎...
Here we are a fucking year later, everybody forgot about the shit...
你嘴里就不能说点别的了?
you go running your mouth about nothing at all?
- 可是 String... - 什么 她也要相信那堆狗屎了
- But, String... - What, and she gonna believe that shit, too.
什么样的妈妈不愿相信 自己的儿子没有自杀?
I mean, what moms is not gonna believe her son didn't kill hisself?
- String... - 嗯? 她就打算一直想着...
- String... - Huh? She gonna take that shit...
把自己弄得半疯
go half-crazy with it.
- 我只是... - 你只是什么?
- I just... - You just what?
对不起!
Sorry!
你什么时候告诉她的?
When you tell her that?
大概一星期前吧 我想
About a week ago, I guess.
她什么时候去找警察?
When is she gonna go see the cop?
她要先和律师谈谈 问问他怎么办
Think she gonna talk to a lawyer first, ask him how to play it.
谁 Levy?
Who, Levy?
可能吧 谁知道 律师
I guess, whoever. The lawyer.
- Levy? - 我猜是吧
- Levy? - I guess.
哦 你没问一下?
Oh, you didn't ask that?
这个该死的Royce 搪塞我
And this fucking Royce just lets it slide.
我去找他 行吧? 不是去跟他理论
I mean, I go to him, right? Not to make points,
只是去做正确的事...  可他除了惹火了我什么都没做
just to do the right thing... what does he do but blow smoke up my ass.
"我很高兴你为此来找我们 Tommy
"I'm glad you came to us with this, Tommy.
"哦 我会如火如荼的办的 别担心
"Oh, I'll light a fire, don't you worry.
我们这就着手去办"
We gotta move on this."
我一直以为他没有种这么玩伎俩
I never thought he'd have the balls to just fuck the dog on it.
- 你在做正确的事 - 操 当然了
- And you were doing the right thing. - Fuck, yeah.
怎么了?
What?
你去找Royce 希望他会失望
You went there hoping that Royce would disappoint.
你是想知道你比他更有 资格坐在他的位子上
You want to know that you're better, that you deserve his chair.
如果我躺在沙发上
If I lie down on this couch,
你会按小时收费吗?
do you charge by the hour?
谢谢
Thanks.
你不天真 我也不
You're not naive. Neither am I.
一个人参加竞选 都会有一点自以为是的感觉
A man doesn't run for office without being a bit self-righteous first.
自以为是? 我?
Self-righteous? Me?
那么你现打算怎么办?
So, what are you gonna do now?
给一两个记者打电话 搞一搞市长 也许从背景入手...
Call a reporter or two, rip the Mayor, maybe on background...
从记录入手也成 我不知道
maybe go on the record, I don't know.
现在就搞他?
Rip him now?
九月份你就要初选了哦?
With the primary next September?
Tommy 没人会记得一个 已经死去一年的证人
Tommy, no one's gonna remember a dead witness a year from now.
更好的方法是 你去找Royce
Better if you go to Royce,
跟他对质 不要愤怒...
confront him, not angrily...
给他个机会解释或者采取行动
give him a chance to explain or maybe take action.
如果他有所行动 而问题也得到解决...
If he does do something, then a problem got fixed...
那你就会因为帮上忙 而感觉很不一般
and you can feel special for helping.
如果他什么也没做 你就静观其变
If he doesn't, you sit tight.
我不知道  也许你在信里记录下你们的会面...
I don't know. Maybe you document your meeting in a letter...
表达出你的关注和遗憾
expressing your concern and regret.
然后下一个证人被害 你就可以主动出击
Then you're set if the next witness gets killed.
双赢
Win-win.
除非你是证人
Unless you're the witness.
我知道 你是对的
I know, you're right.
但是他在寻求连任
But he's taking on a two-term incumbent.
事情会因此而变得丑陋不堪
It's all gonna be ugly from here.
好吧
All right.
是 没问题
Yeah, it's cool.
到星期一还要30 行吧?
Need another 30 by Monday, all right?
好的
All right.
是
Yeah.
差点忘了这个
Forgot this.
贱人 我说的每件事你都给听反了
Bitch, everything I say, you hear backwards.
白痴混蛋
Stupid motherfucker.
我有T恤 白色亮闪闪!
Got them T's, white and bright!
一件3块 两件5块
One for $3, two for $5.
蓝头 有蓝头!
Blue tops, got them blue tops!
我有T恤
I got them T's.
白色 亮闪闪 一件3块 两件5块
White, bright, one for $3, two for $5.
- 我有这个 兄弟 5块 新鲜的 - 不用了 谢谢 兄弟
- I got this, man, $5. New. - No, thank you, man.
- 就5块钱 - 不了 谢谢
- It's only $5. - No, thank you.
操你 杂种 操你
Fuck you, then, man, fuck you. Fuck you.
我有...
I got them...
我有 我有T恤
I got them. I got them t's.
红头 红头 有红头!
Red tops, red tops, got them red tops!
Rockefeller 有rockefeller 嘿!
Rockefeller, got some rockefeller, hey!
嘿 卖货的 都有什么货?
Hey, seller man, what you got?
有年轻人用的长白色T恤
Got the long white t's for the young ones.
你有蜡烛吗? 我想买蜡烛...
You ain't got no candles? I'm looking to buy candles...
还有厕所用的手纸
and toilet paper for the shit-Bucket, too.
- 你明天还在这儿吗? - 我不能走
- You be back here tomorrow? - I can't leave.
我一走 位置就被抢了
I leave, somebody grab my stake.
我明天再来
I'll be back tomorrow.
嗨 Johnny
Yo, johnny.
你好吗 伙计?
What's up, bubs?
妈的 Johnny 兄弟
Shit, johnny, man.
一直在抽 知道么?
Just been chasing the pipe, you know?
那玩意让我把膀子都抓烂了
Shit's got me all digging and scratching in my arms.
没事的
You know, it's cool.
好吧 来吧 兄弟 你需要歇歇 知道吗?
All right. Come on, man, you need a break, all right?
说真的 兄弟 你得休息 来吧 兄弟
I'm serious, man, you need a break. Come on, man.
不用 兄弟 你四处看看
No, man, look around you.
这就是士兵的天堂 兄弟
It's a soldier's paradise, man.
我是个海盗 伙计
I'm a viking, bubs.
你是海盗吗?
Are you a viking?
操 又来了
Fuck, not again.
- 你们俩过去吗? - 长官说把他们弄到这来
- You two coming? -Major said to bring them down here,
他没说让我们他妈扮奶妈 照顾这群该死的畜牲
He didn't say shit about playing nursemaid to a bunch of goddamn animals.
往后退 退后 往后退
Push it back. Get back, push it back.
- 我们把他们都铐上吗 警官? - 不用 放了他们
- Should we cuff them, sarge? - No, cut them loose.
我们他妈不是告诉你们 别在这儿打架?
The fuck we tell you about fighting down here?
就一条规则 不打架 不动刀 不开枪!
Only rule is no fighting, no cutting, no shooting!
你们还是弄得一团糟
Y'all still fuck it up.
下次你再把我弄到这儿来
Next time you make me come down here,
看我会不会呼叫10-38
see if i don't call for a 10-38.
你应该知道 白痴 那是叫救护车
Just so you know, dickhead, that's an ambulance.
散了 散了 都散了
Break it up, break it up, break it up.
我是不是把孩子吵醒了?
Did i wake the baby?
要是吵醒了你会知道
You would know if you did.
凌晨3点 很高兴你还回来
3:00 in the morning. Nice of you to check in.
- 下班以后我去放松了一下 - 是啊 你看上去是挺放松的
- I went out after work to unwind. - Yeah, you look unwound.
好吧
Well.
我想家里有你一切就都井井有条了
I figured you had everything under control on the home front.
你他妈怎么回事?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
你这是讽刺谁呢?  你和谁都能谈怎么就不找我谈?
What's with the sarcasm? How come you can talk to everybody else but me?
你真想知道?
Do you really want to know?
说吧
I'm listening.
我怀念就我们两个的日子
I miss us.
别怪在孩子身上 别这样
Do not blame that baby. Do not do it.
- 我不怪任何人 - 这不是我一个人的决定
- I'm not blaming anybody. - I didn't do this by myself.
我们商量过 所有的事情
We discussed it, all of it.
我们是谈过 没错
We talked about it, yeah.
可是...
But...
我的话语权没有你的多
i didn't have as much to say about it as you.
为什么?
And why not?
因为你...
Because you...
是你想要这样的
you wanted this.
我只是... 我不想让你失望
I just... i didn't want to disappoint you on it.
那我想我不会比现在更失望了
Well, i don't think i could be more disappointed than i am right now.
你走吧
You need to go.
你有多少?
How much you got?
整晚都没事?
Quiet overnight?
午夜那班把一棒子想扫荡这地方的家伙 驱逐出去了 不过...
Midnight shift had to toss a crew that was casing the place, but ...
除此之外 就没了
Other than that...
太多小屁孩儿了
too many damn children.
要是这勾当合法 还要放哨的和跑腿的干什么?
What do you need lookouts and runners for if the shit is legal?
他们中的很多人都被毒贩放了羊了
A lot of them have been cut loose by the dealers.
这就像动物世界
It's like one of those nature shows.
当你搞乱环境  有些物种就他妈被踢出他们的栖息地了
When you mess with the environment some species get fucked out of their habitat.
你刚才用了"栖息地"这个词?
Did you just use the word "habitat" in a sentence?
用了
I did.
给帮你放哨的放大假了 嗯?
Letting your lookouts go, huh?
还有给我跑腿的 妈的 怎么了?
My runners, too. Shit, what's the point?
所以你就在这儿赚大钱...
So, here you are making money hand over fist...
还他妈贪钱贪得连你手下都不管了
and you're too damn greedy to take care of your workforce.
我不需要他们
I don't need them.
但他们需要你 对吧?
But they need you, right?
你不能在街角做生意的时候 除了拉生意的和跑腿的 他们就全靠你了...
You was all they had when you couldn't work a corner except for touts and runners...
当时让他们旷课误工 你可是也在所不惜啊
then it was cool to have them cut school and work out.
听着 税收新方案 兄弟
Okay, new tax initiative, my brother.
你说什么?
Say what?
今后你要还想在Hamsterdam混...
If you wanna sling in hamsterdam after today...
你和其他白痴 每人每星期交100块
you and every other knucklehead, you each got to kick in $100 a week.
哦 你还开始赚外快了 嗯?
Oh, so you trying to get paid, huh?
不是给我 不是
Not me, not for me.
把钱准备好 我会再来
Get the cash up, i'll be back.
- 绿头!绿头! - 怎么了?
- Green tops! Green tops! - What's up?
有绿头
Got the green tops.
但我不会因此进监狱 对吧?
But it ain't something i'm gonna go to jail for, right?
我是说 不会那样的 是不是?
I mean, it ain't nothing like that, is it?
那个?
That one?
不是 要比银色黑一点
No, it was more black than silver.
我想是这个
This one, i think.
我就知道你们要让我干坏事
I can see y'all got some real ugly shit planned for me.
我就知道
I can see it.
你只是碰上了一个聪明的警察  仅此而已
You just bumped up against a clever police is all.
当然 他想用那个死了的姑娘...
Course, he gonna try to shame you with the dead girl...
或者那群崇拜Omar和他的轶事的孩子的事 让你觉得丢脸
or some mess about children looking up to omar and his sawed-Off.
他所能做的...
All he can do...
尤其是在你在那证人的事儿之后 已经开始收敛之后
especially since you backed down what he had for a witness.
就是想让你有负罪感 孩子
He working you with guilt, boy.
是 可那个胖子搅得我不得安宁 Butchie
Yeah, but that fat man gave me a itch i can't scratch, butchie.
哦 这世上每个人都各司其职
Oh, everybody in this world does what they going to.
我 你 还有警察
Me, you, the police.
这世上的每个人都有自己的位置
Everybody in this world got their own place.
如果干你这行的人开始
And a man in your line of work start
担心别人怎么看自己
worrying about how other people see you.
学着做别人而不做自己 那他就离死不远了
Playing to other people instead of to hisself, he gonna get dead.
我还是觉得欠别人的 Butch
I still feel like i owe something, butch.
我有个叔叔 在南卡罗莱纳
I had a uncle down carolina,
他已经死了...
he dead now...
但我一直记得他因为把女友赶走...
but i remember he was grieving real hard...
而非常非常伤心
real hard over chasing his ladyfriend away.
所以 他就惩罚自己
So, he put himself to punishment.
用刀把自己的小手指和无名指剁下来
Took a knife to his little finger, then his ring finger.
血淋淋地扔在桌上 然后他突然就醒悟了
With them all bloody on the table, he pulled up short.
在他后半辈子...
For the rest of his life...
我记得他说  "这贱人连根小手指头都抵不上"
i remember him saying, "the bitch wasn't worth more than a pinkie."
但那时已经太晚了
But it was too late then.
你要是想可以试试
You can try that if you got a mind.
我不知道 Butch
I don't know, butch.
不用走那种极端吧
A little something less dramatical.
是啊
You feel me?
- 你了解吗? - 恩
- You feel me? - mm.
是你告诉Brianna 可以去市中心谈这个吗?
You told brianna she could go downtown with this?
D'angelo是他的儿子  我怎么能阻止她?
D'angelo's her son, how was i gonna stop her?
听着 听着 只要她闭嘴听着 就不会有什么事的
Look. Look, there's no harm done if she keeps her mouth shut and just listens.
不对 这事搞砸了
No, it's fucked up.
不能再有这种电话去打搅Brianna
There ain't no call messing with brianna with this bullshit.
- 你能做什么? - 我不知道
- What can you do? - I don't know.
提交一份对警探的投诉或者什么东西 我不知道
File a complaint against the detective or some shit. I don't know.
骚扰?
Harassment?
听着 这和办Avon案子的是同一个混蛋
Look, this is the same motherfucker that had avon's case.
同一个混蛋到我的打印店  跟我说那堆狗屎
Same motherfucker that's coming at me in my print shop, talking shit...
现在 他又去找Brianna胡说八道?
and now, he coming at brianna with this bullshit?
投诉根本没什么用
A complaint's not going to do anything.
而且事实上...
And the fact is...
如果警察说她儿子可能不是自杀...
if the cops are saying her son might not be a suicide...
Brianna不管如何都会想听一听的
brianna's gonna hear this out, regardless.
不过 我想应该让Avon知道这些
I suppose avon should know about it, though.
是啊 交给我吧
Yeah, well, i'll handle that.
这里没什么动静嘛
Not much slinging going on here.
西区的孩子们正坐拥他们的房产呢
Western boys are sitting on the real estate.
是 好的 好的 他们也会做的
Yeah. All right. All right. That'll work too.
好的
All right.
嘿 Shamrock说我们应该带些人到Hamsterdam 在那儿把货都卖了
Yo, shamrock says we should take some of our people down to hamsterdam and sell off there.
至少 在这些缉毒警察离开部分街角之前
At least, until these narcos roll up off some of these corners.
- 来吧 - 是 是
- Come on. - Yeah. Yeah.
来吧
Come on.
- 停车检查? - 为什么不呢?
- Car stop, maybe? - Why not?
- 嘿 混蛋 - 这儿就有 嘿!
- Hey, motherfucker. - Got it right here, yo!
有粉头 呦
Get that pink top, yo.
还没完 你个他妈的老鼠!
Not yet, you fucking rodent!
你们不能这么干 兄弟 我们要去Hamsterdam
Y'all can't do this, man. We headed to hamsterdam.
你再从那车上下来 你就要去Bon Secours急诊室 听见了吗?
You come off that car again.You headed to bon secours emergency room. You hear me?
嘿 警官 你们不能抓我们 我们要去自由区
Yo, officer, we got immunity from y'all. We going to the free zone.
什么他妈自由区?
What the fuck's a free zone?
- 要出手的货 - 我说 说真的
- Package for sale. - I'm saying, straight up.
你们为什么一开始就认为 我们是去那儿?
Why you think we was headed there in the first place?
趴下
Get down.
- 去哪儿? - Hamsterdam
- Headed where? - Hamsterdam.
操你 都是狗屁
Suck my dick!
嘿  你们都想被抓起来?
Hey, y'all wanna see a wagon?
操你们的!贱人们
Fuck y'all!
你他妈现在能闭上你的臭嘴吗?
Will you shut the fuck up and cut this shit out now?
按你说的
Like you said.
这是收条
That's your receipt.
244块是篮框钱 给我...
$244 for the hoop comes back to me...
凑个整数 250块 是汽油钱
rounded to $250 for my gas money.
这是还我的
This repays me.
剩下这些?
And the rest of this?
用来付给这星期的小混混
Use it to pay them hoppers for the week.
不管你用不用  这些钱你都要给出去
Whether you use them or not, you pay this money out.
这就像失业保险
This shit is like unemployment insurance.
每个雇员都要交钱
Every employer gotta pay in.
如果我发现谁没交钱 那他就别在这儿混了
If i find out anybody been holding out then he's out of here,
滚回街上 弄个头破血流
back in the street getting his head busted.
你们至少能做的就是  照顾照顾你们自己人
The least you all can do is look after your own people a little bit.
怎么着 你成了他妈共产党啦?
What are you, a fucking communist?
23-04 需要几个10-16s 去Fayette 西vincent
23-04. Need a couple of 10-16s to fayette, west of vincent.
- 从这儿拐过去就是 - 收到 车辆接警出动
- That's right around the corner from here. - 10-4. Units responding.
他妈怎么回事?
What the fuck happened?
停车检查
Car stop.
在副驾座位下面发现发现g粉
I got a g-Pack from beneath the passenger seat.
嘿 我们正要去Hamsterdam
Yo, we was on our way to hamsterdam.
这人说我们可以随便出入 怎么回事?
The man say we don't get no hassle coming in or going out. What's up?
Hamsterdam是他妈什么地方?
What the fuck is hamsterdam?
混蛋骗子警察!
Lying-Ass police!
你不能抓他
I can't let you do this.
那可是g芬
Carv, they got a g-pack.
在自由区 他们可以的 你知道规则的
On the way to free zone, they did. You know the rules.
就是 兄弟 我一直跟他们说...
Yeah, man and i was trying to tell these people...
你他妈闭嘴
just shut the fuck up.
请抵达Fayette和Vincent的小队回话
700 To any unit at the scene at fayette and vincent.
在 头儿?
Yeah, boss?
你那边什么情况?
You got a situation there?
- 真不敢相信这狗屁东西 - 是啊 可狗屁可不对
- I can't believe this bullshit. - Yeah, bullshit is right.
- 我跟你说了他妈的闭嘴 - 嘿 兄弟 你他妈的保证过的!
- I told you to shut the fuck up. - Yo, man, you gave us y'all fucking word!
你自己清楚 兄弟 搞他妈什么飞机啊
You know you did, man. This is some fucking bullshit.
你们都是他妈的骗子 兄弟
Y'all some fucking liars, man.
Carv 你能告诉我这他妈到底怎么回事吗?
Carv, will you please tell me what the fuck is going on here?
警长说他马上过来
Major said he's on his way.
Carv?
哦 天哪
Oh, man.
你确定是这个?
You sure that's the one?
Reesie说就是这个
Reesie say that was the one.
我算老几 能说不是吗?
Who am i to say different?
告诉他 这东西确认之后我才会付钱
Tell him i ain't gonna pay till it proves itself, though.
我已经告诉他了
I told him that already.
他说解决这个麻烦要1500块
He say $1,500 for his troubles.
妈的
Damn.
良心是有代价的
Conscience do cost.
我看见他了 Bernard 你连那扇门都没进去...
I seen him, bernard. You hadn't even gone past the damn door...
他就把那些纸全扔进垃圾箱了
and he threw all them papers in the trash.
你在说谎 我能看出来
You lying now, i could tell.
你是唯一在乎这事的人...
You is the only one who gives a fuck...
你要不是我曾经约会过的傻逼...
and if you hadn't been the stupidest motherfucker that i ever gone out with...
就能马上买下一堆那东西
you just would have bought a whole bunch of them things at once.
我再买6个就行了 差不多一个半小时我们就能走了
I only need like six more. We be done in like a half an hour.
要不我们多停一站 你去买那6个狗屁东西...
How about we make one more stop, you get six of them shits...
现在我给你吹个20分钟
and i suck your dick for the next 20 minutes.
成啦
Got you.
操
Oh, fuck.
操你们的
Oh, fuck you all.
- 妈的 我上双分班了 兄弟  - 是啊 是啊
- Shit, i worked a double, man. - Yeah, right.
- Bunk 3号线 - 好的
- Bunk, line three. - All right.
把它钉在板子上 Mike 你知道怎么做
Tack it to the board, mike, you know the rules.
Moreland警探
Detective moreland.
听说你在找东西
Heard you looking for something.
我要几个激活的一次性手机
Let me get some of them trac phones activated.
买8个那玩意
Eight of them bitches.
这个是在地段2
This one's for sector two.
在地段1  我用的是Winchester的低层空屋
Sector one, i'm using that empty low-Rise housing on winchester.
在地段3 是老的厂房
Sector three, the old koppers plant.
在这儿交易是合法的?
And it's legal to sell here?
不合法
It's not legal.
我们只是在另辟蹊径
We just look the other way is all.
怎么能? 你怎么能这样?
How? How can you?
听着 我知道你现在很难接受...
Look, i know it hurts your head to think about...
但是在你发脾气之前...
but before you decide to lose your mind on this...
用点时间 到我管辖的街角 那些最差的贩毒据点去看看
take a moment, ride around to my corners, my worst drug corners.
Edmondson和Brice 北部和Pulaski Hollins和Payson
Edmondson and brice. North and pulaski. Hollins and payson.
都干净了 所有这些地方
They're empty. All of them.
整个地区 我的犯罪率下降了5%
District-Wide, my crime is down 5%.
可上头知道吗?
But do the bosses know?
不知道 上头的人根本不管
No, the bosses don't know shit about it.
听着 是地区指挥官自己采取行动
Look, this is just a district commander taking initiative on his own.
我的天哪!
Jesus christ!
我知道这事被捅到市里 只是时间问题
I knew it was a matter of time before i bumped into somebody from downtown about this.
我也知道你们自然而然 想把你们的所见所闻上报
And i know your natural impulse is to take what you saw back downtown with you.
- 但我要让你们... - 你这是纵容贩毒!
- But i got to ask you... - you legalized drugs!
听着 这是战略部署
Look, this is a tactical deployment.
等这三个地区的事情尘埃落定...
We just wait for everything to get settled down here in these three zones...
我们就继续下一步
and then we move.
听着 我们大规模抓人造造声势 然后就关掉这里
Look, we make a big show of locking everybody up and then we shut it down.
很抱歉把你的逮捕行动给搅黄了
I'm sorry i had to fuck you up on that arrest.
也很抱歉让你看着 我把g粉还给那帮小兔崽子
And i'm sorry you had to see me give that runt back the g-Pack.
这事儿很恶心 我知道
That was ugly, i know.
但我只是尽力去收拾我辖区内的烂摊子 用尽各种方法 只要我能做到
But i'm just trying to save what's left of my district any way i can, if i can.
在我必须向上头汇报这个部署之前 我的时间越多...
And the longer i have before i have to brief the bosses about this deployment...
我们已经从停车检查中找到需要的东西  警长 不用担心
We got all we needed from the car stop, major. Don't sweat it.
让我跟我的老长官说几句话
Let me get a word with my old commander.
我不知道 警长
I don't know, major.
不管你什么时候整顿这地方 他们还是会回到原来的位置
Whenever you bust this place up, they'll go back to their same corners.
而且 你从来都不擅长造声势
Besides, you were never much on making a big show.
如果这办法行不通 Jimmy 我是说 那一切又照旧了
If this doesn't work, jimmy, i mean, it's just back to usual.
无论如何 我都得拿着退休金滚蛋
I'm out the door on pension anyway.
Jimmy 我还需要时间
Jimmy, i need more time.
我需要依靠你和你们 这些人来完成
I need to be able to rely on you and your people to keep this close.
上头的人都不知道 嗯?
Bosses don't know, huh?
操他们上头的
Fuck the bosses.
你是那个打电话的人?
You the man who called?
恩
mm-uhm.
是我打的
I did.
你是目击者还是什么?
You witnessing or what?
恐怕我看不见
I'm afraid i'm blind.
真瞎了
Legally.
倒是有东西让你看
Something you need to see, though.
我想一定是Glock40
Glock.40, I believe.
我想你是不会告诉我 是谁把这个带来的吧?
I suppose you ain't going to tell me who brought this here, right?
我说了 我看不见
Like I said, I'm blind.
不过我想你也许知道
I thought you might know, though.
你可以告诉他 是我说的...
You can tell him from me...
我希望总有一天 在法庭上他可能用得上这个
I'm hoping he might need this in court some day.
兄弟 缉毒警可能会回来
Man, narcos might come back.
可能会
They might.
不过在他们回来之前 这地盘还是你的
But until they do, this your corner to hold.
Marlo的人呢?
What about Marlo's crew?
听着 Avon家的...
Look, Avon's home...
你在Barksdale街角 你明白吗?
and you on a Barksdale corner. You feel me?
- Avon现在不在 - 你有人手
- Avon ain't here now. - You got muscle.
不用担心 小伙子
Don't worry about that, little man.
嘿
Hey.
年轻的Bodie Broadus的手机
The burner of young Bodie Broadus.
还剩几分钟
Still has minutes left.
快捷键?
Speed dial?
- Caroline - 嗯?
- Caroline. - huh?
你那儿有多余的房间吗?
You wouldn't have an extra room at your place, would you?
我就住一两个晚上 直到我的破事处理完
Just for a night or two till I can get my shit together.
还没好呢?
Ain't no fixing it?
好得很呢 我想
It's fixed pretty good, I think.
- 谢了 - 嗯
- Thanks. - mm-uhm.
信用卡是登记在Theresa D'Agostino名下的 一个公司账户
Credit card was a business account listed to a Theresa D'Agostino.
对 就是她
Yeah, that's her.
什么公司?
What kind of business?
民主党国会竞选委员会
Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee.
通过信用卡账单追查到 公司地址在Washington西北部
Billing on the card goes to a business address in northwest Washington.
我给总机打了电话 她已经被记下了
I called the switchboard and she's listed.
D'Agostino听上去不像 西巴尔的摩人的名字
D'Agostino doesn't sound much like a West Baltimore name to me.
我觉得也是
Me, either.
说实话 我不知道我想要什么
Truth is, I don't know what I want.
我知道我在找东西
I know I'm looking for something,
可连找的是什么我都说不上来
but I can't even tell you what it is.
我听说你找到工作了
I understand you found work.
没工资 不过我打算干
Ain't no payroll job, but it'll do.
你来这儿不是为了找工作 或是参加一般同等学历培训
You ain't here for a job or the GED program.
那么你想加入教会?
So, you looking to join the church?
我...
I...
我只是...
I just...
很长时间了 我一直觉得...
I've had this feeling for a long time...
好像我灵魂出窍...
and it's like I'm standing outside myself...
看着自己做些 我根本不想做的事 你知道吗?
watching me do things I don't wanna do, you know?
我就好像旁观者...
Just seeing me like I'm somebody else...
但是根本不能阻止这些
but never, ever being able to stop the show.
我很累
I'm tired.
是Cutty的事 对吗?
It's Cutty, right?
不是 老兄
No, man.
是Dennis
Dennis.
- 她走了 嗯? - 她离开办公室了
- She's left, huh? - She's out of the office.
我想 事实上 我今天应该和她见面的
I figured that, 'cause I'm supposed to meet her, actually.
今晚 好的
Tonight, yeah.
是的 没错
Right, exactly.
我本来要去接她然后带她去的 可是我迟到了
Well, I was going to pick her up and take her to that, but I'm running late.
- 她的计划可能有变 - 是 是 我知道
- Her plans may have changed. - Yeah, yeah, I know.
那地方具体在哪儿? 我对那边真的不熟...
Where is that e xactly? I'm not real familiar with that part of...
在第15大街的拐角...
It's on the corner of 15th Street and...
好的
Okay.
很不幸 该死的日程安排都冲突了
Too many damn scheduling conflicts, unfortunately.
不过我们已经把这事列入 下次会议的日程上了
But we have put it on the agenda for the next meeting
刑事司法协调委员会的会议
of the Coordinating Council on Criminal Justice.
您要提交给委员会?
You're sentencing it to committee?
市长先生 我们只要几十万的启动经费
Mr. Mayor, we're probably only talking, like, a few hundred thousand to start.
我不是说要给这些人新的身份...
I'm not saying we should create new identities for these people...
再像联邦调查局那样 把他们送到新墨西哥
send them to New Mexico like the Feds.
我们只需要让他们远离危险
We just need to get them out of harm's way.
告诉你吧 议员
Let me tell you something, Councilman.
没有上头批准  我根本拿不到几十万美元
I can't lay my hands on several hundred thousand dollars that's not already spoken for.
- 市长先生 我不是... - 你想让我做什么 议员?
- Mr. Mayor, I was not... - What would you have me do, Councilman?
让我把预算用作第一区 今年冬天扫雪的钱
Should I divert the money that's already been budgeted for snow removal
挪作他用?
from the First District this winter?
要不我削减每周 全市的垃圾清理费...
Or how about I reduce trash pickup to once a week citywide...
用这些钱把目击证人 都送到Hyatt内港去?
put the witnesses up at the Hyatt Inner Harbor?
我不想为难你 Tommy 真的
I'm not trying to be difficult. Tommy, come on.
市里现在财政紧张?
The city in the financial situation it's in?
Annapolis的朋友不对啊
Very few friends in Annapolis.
目前 对这件事我们已经尽力而为了
We've done all we could do with this matter for now.
那好吧
Okay, then.
谢谢你抽时间见我 先生们
Thanks for your time. Gentlemen.
啊 妈的
Ah, what the fuck.
我不知道 头儿  如果这没这么多死孩子
I don't know, boss. If there weren't so many fucking kids down here,
我也许觉得还好
I might be okay with it.
巴尔的摩警察
Baltimore police.
巴尔的摩?
Baltimore?
巴尔的摩 马里兰州
Baltimore, Maryland.
- 能给我来杯Jameson吗? - Bushmills的可以吗?
- Can I get a Jameson? - Bushmills okay?
那是新教徒喝的威士忌
That's Protestant whiskey.
但价格公道 是吧?
The price is right, isn't it?
不掺水
Make it neat.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
你怎么来了?
What are you doing here?
我也这么问我自己
Just asking myself the same thing.
你大老远地开车跑到这 就是为了看我穿过房间然后就走?
You drive all the way down here to look at me from across the room and then leave?
那可有点恐怖啊
That's kind of creepy.
你看起来很忙啊
You looked occupied.
他吗? 亲爱的 公事而已
Him? Honey, that's just business.
- 这不是我呆的地方 - 肯定不是
- This ain't my kind of crowd. - Definitely not.
是啊 我就不该来 还是赶快走吧
Yeah, well, I made a mistake, so I better go.
428房?
428?
你就住在城里
You live in this town.
- 为什么还要订房间? - 我住在城那头
- Why book the room? - I live across town.
怕搞得太晚 酒后驾车啊
As late as these things go, that's a DUI away.
给我两小时行吗 McNulty?
Give me two hours, McNulty?
那我这两小时都干什么?
What am I gonna do for two hours?
做美梦
Dream on it.
来点儿水不?
Water fresh?
你把他们都摆平了?
You keeping them cool?
你有幼鸽乳鸽啊
You got squeakers nesting squabs.
好好照顾小鸽子 我喜欢
Taking care of the young'uns. I like seeing that.
是 Marlo 他很忠心
Yeah, Marlo, he's real loyal.
我都没法把他从笼子里弄出去
I can't kick him off that nest.
干得不错 真的不错
This is good work. This is really good work.
警察去清理那些街角了
Police coming off them corners.
我看见了
I seen.
看来我暂时做不了生意了
Gonna keep my name off the package for a time,
只能做批发
gonna keep wholesaling.
退后一步
You know, step back a bit.
Barksdale该觉得我们服软了
Barksdale gonna think we weak,
现在可不是出来抢地盘的时候
not coming out to claim what's ours.
警察一离开那些街角 他就会回去
The police leave them corners, he's gonna be back out there.
我知道
I know he will.
你说吧 姑娘
Your turn, girl.
是时候了 真的
It's about time. For real.
首先...
For starters...
手机记录了使用者打出 或者接到的最后10个电话
its memory holds the last 10 calls made and received by the user.
- 足够让我们发现标识了 - 标识?
- That's enough to give us a signature. - Signature?
每个人的号码都是独一无二的
The phone number's unique to an individual.
这样我们就能在使用者 换另一部手机的时候识别出他的身份
That way we can identify the user when he switches to another phone.
抱歉 迟到了 在别的地方过夜来着
Sorry, I'm late. Woke up in the wrong town.
总之 我们查了查这些号码的收费记录...
Anyway, we ran the tolls on those numbers...
得出一种很有趣的模式
and we came up with a rather interesting pattern.
看看这个  这是一个封闭的通讯网络模式
Check this out. This is the pattern of a closed communication network.
是属于贩毒组织的网络
Something you'd expect from a drug organization.
这个网络到目前为止 一共有15个直接的一次性手机
This particular one so far involves 15 distinct burners.
- 15个 - 嗯
- 15. - mm.
而且他们没有一个列出了用户信息
And none of them list subscriber information.
- 可以这样吗? - 就这些一次性的 这种公司
- You can do that? - With these burners with this particular company,
根本不需要用户信息
you don't need subscriber information.
我们的数据表明 超过92%的电话
Our data shows that over 92% of the calls
都是在这个网络内打的
were made within this network,
平均每个电话时间不超过一分钟
with the average call lasting less than a minute.
再一次证明 应该就是毒品交易
Again, suggestive of drug trafficking.
现在 看这个使用者 他就像是一个交流中心
Now, this user here, he serves as a clearing house.
他接电话 并且打出电话
He receives calls and initiates interactions.
- 他来协调整个交易 - 要是Stringer就太好了
- He coordinates the show. - Nice if that was Stringer.
现在是最精彩的地方 Prez在鼓捣手机的时候
Now, this is the best part. This is something
发现了一些东西
that Prez discovered when he was playing with it.
这手机被设置过快捷键
It has a speeddial feature.
意思是 有人花时间
Meaning, someone took the time
给这部手机编了程序
to program the phone.
见鬼 这可能是这帮街头小子 唯一能记住所有号码的方法
Hell, that's probably the only way these corner boys can remember all the numbers.
用这些隔几天就被扔掉的手机
What with these phones being dumped every few days or so.
我敢打赌 网络中的其他手机 都是同样的设置
I'll bet all the other phones in the network are set up the same way.
好了 我明白了 我们应该从监听电话入手
Well, I've heard enough. We should start writing for the wire.
- 我们什么时候能监听? - 监听什么?
- When can we get up? - Get up on what?
他们平均每隔几周就换手机
They're dumping phones every couple of weeks on average.
等你追踪到的时候 这些手机已经没用了
By the time you get a wire up on that, the phones are dead.
同时 整个网络也会关闭
The whole network shuts down simultaneously.
- 那我们有什么办法吗? - 目前还没有
- Do we have a plan? - Not yet, we don't.
不过 目前如果我能再弄到 几部这种废弃的手机...
But, for now, if I could get a couple more of these dead phones...
应该能帮助证明 书面证词的理论
it'd probably help corroborate the theory for the affidavit.
Kima 这几天你能让那些西部的小子
Kima, maybe you could ask those Western boys
捡一些他们在地上发现的手机吗?
to pick up what they find on the ground for the next few days. Huh?
好的 没问题
Yeah, sure.
该死 哥们儿 你一股子做爱的味道
Damn, boy, you smell like sex.
- 你他妈连个澡都不洗? - 我上班都迟到了
- You didn't take a fucking shower? - I was late for work.
你把我的Newports给忘了吧?
Forgot my Newports, didn't you?
哦 妈的 忘了 兄弟
Oh, shit, man, I did, yo.
我吃完薯片就去拿你的烟
Let me do these chips and then I'll go get your cigarettes.
操
Fuck.
3-1 枪击 一名男性
3-1 on shooting of this number one male.
请求支援
We're gonna need 10-100 down here.
收到...我马上出发
Copy that... I'm on my way.
- Roger 700 - 这么快就回来了?
- Roger, 700. - Back so soon?
我以为你们昨天已经在 我们的欢乐地盘呆够了
I thought you guys had enough of our happy district yesterday.
帮个忙吧 Lester让你把在Barksdale的地盘...
Just need a favor. Lester wants you to scoop up...
发现的所有废弃手机都搜集起来
any discarded cell phones you find on Barksdale corners.
Barksdale的汽车牌照  标牌号码都要吗?
You want Barksdale's license plates. Tag numbers and all?
有什么要什么
Whatever, sure.
我前两天看见个大块头 开着辆卡车
'Cause I saw big man riding in a truck the other day.
没看清标牌  不过要是我能再看见他...
Missed the tags, but if I see him again...
Stringer?
- 不是 是另一个 - 什么另一个?
- No, the other guy. - What other guy?
大块头 我们以前抓过他
Big boy, the one we locked up.
- Avon - Avon Barksdale?
- Avon. - Avon Barksdale?
天哪 Herc 他在Jessup呢 至少要关四五年
Jesus, Herc. He's at Jessup, down for four or five at least.
怎么 你看我们都挺像吧?
What, we all look alike to you?
你们要是不信 去他妈的
If you don't believe me, fuck it.
没门
No fucking way.
但事实仍然如此
But the fact remains,
没有巴尔的摩市民的协助
we would not be returning this service weapon to this officer
我们就不能把这件武器 交还给这位警官
without help from the citizens of Baltimore as well.
关于这一点
And on that note,
我们的市长还有话要说
I think our Mayor would like to say a few words.
谢谢你 Burrell局长 我只想借此机会
Thank you, Commissioner Burrell. I just want to take this opportunity
表扬警局成功破获这起案件
to commend our department on successfully resolving this case
并且希望Dozerman警官 能够早日回到工作岗位
and to wish Officer Dozerman a speedy return to duty.
Dozerman警官
Officer Dozerman,
亲爱的Royce市长 我很感谢你 抽时间就证人协助项目与我见面 我个人还是很担忧...
市民希望你把这个拿回去...
the citizens want you to have this back...
并对你履行保护城市的职责 表示感谢
and to thank you for your service in defense of our city.
我还要特别感谢 所有的热心居民...
And I especially want to thank all of our concerned residents...
他们拨打了热线电话 否则我们今天就不会在这里...
who called in to the hotline. We would not be here today...
Lester
Lester.
队长 你得看看这个
Lieutenant, you gotta see this.
取保释放 04年9月24日
真是笑话
Big joke.
以此纪念Geraldine Peroni 编辑 同事 朋友 1953-2004